export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `What year was FBLA founded?`,
        options: [`1940`, `1955`, `1985`, `2000`],
        answer: `1940`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `Hamden L. Forkner founded FBLA.`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: `FBLA is mainly funded through leadership dues.`,
        options: [`False`, `True`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `How many National Fall Leadership Conferences are held each year?`,
        options: [`3`, `1`, `4`, `2`],
        answer: `4`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `What is the FBLA National Theme?`,
        options: [`Create Lead Inspire`, `Create Lead Impact`, `Serve Lead Grow`, `Future Business Leaders of America`],
        answer: `Create Lead Inspire`
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: `Where was the 2019 National Leadership Conference?`,
        options: [`Chicago IL`, `San Antonio TX`, `Orlando FL`, `Boston MA`],
        answer: `San Antonio TX`
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: `What year was the grand opening of FBLA-PBL national center held?`,
        options: [`1990`, `1991`, `2001`, `1997`],
        answer: `1991`
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: `Total Number of FBLA national officers:`,
        options: [`10`, `5`, `15`, `9`],
        answer: `9`
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: `The State Conference is usually held in which month?`,
        options: [`June`, `March`, `August`, `December`],
        answer: `March`
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: `The PBL Division was created in 1957`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: `PBL stands for Phi Beta Lambda`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: `What are the official colors of FBLA-PBL?`,
        options: [`Blue and Gold`, `Purple and Yellow`, `Red and White`],
        answer: `Blue and Gold`
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: `Which month is FBLA-PBL Week held in?`,
        options: [`February`, `April`, `October`],
        answer: `February`
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: `The three categories of competitive events are Individual, Team, and Chapter`,
        options: [`False`, `True`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: `When is American Enterprise Day?`,
        options: [`November 15`, `October 21`, `May 15`],
        answer: `November 15`
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: `Who was the first executive director of FBLA?`,
        options: [`Gayle Robinson`, `Kelly Scholl`, `Dr Edward Miller`],
        answer: `Dr Edward Miller`
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: `What year was the professional division created?`,
        options: [`1995`, `1985`, `1989`],
        answer: `1989`
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: `Illinois was the first state to receive an FBLA charter`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: `The 3 words on the FBLA Emblem are Service, Education, Progress`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: `In what month is FBLA Week celebrated?`,
        options: [`October`, `June`, `February`],
        answer: `February`
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: `Casual attire is acceptable for FBLA activities`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: `The concept of FBLA was developed at what university?`,
        options: [`Columbia`, `Harvard`, `Yale`],
        answer: `Columbia`
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: `FBLA started out as a collegiate organization`,
        options: [`False`, `True`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: `What charitable organization does FBLA primarily support?`,
        options: [`Habitat for Humanity`, `Red Cross`, `March of Dimes`, `St. Jude's`],
        answer: `March of Dimes`
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: `The term of office for a National Officer begins at the close of NLC`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: `The Parliamentary Procedure Event is named after`,
        options: [`Edward Miller`, `Dorothy L. Travis`, `John Roberts`],
        answer: `Dorothy L. Travis`
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        question: `What parliamentary procedures(off which book) do FBLA meetings follow?`,
        options: [`Robert's Rules`, `Laura's Laws`, `The FBLA Charter`],
        answer: `Robert's Rules`
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        question: `When was the Alumni Division founded?`,
        options: [`1989`, `1960`, `1979`],
        answer: `1979`
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        question: `National Community Service Day is on February 15`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 29,
        question: `How many FBLA goals are there?`,
        options: [`9`, `6`, `10`, `5`],
        answer: `9`
    },
    {
        id: 30,
        question: `A ruling is a formal proposal by a member suggesting that the assembly take a certain action.`,
        options: [`False`, `True`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 31,
        question: `How many members does FBLA-PBL have?`,
        options: [`100,000`, `150,000`, `375,000`, `250,000`],
        answer: `250,000`
    },
    {
        id: 32,
        question: `FBLA-PBL's National Center located in Reston, VA`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        question: `What two words are repeated throughout the FBLA-PBL creed?`,
        options: [`I serve`, `I impact`, `I believe`],
        answer: `I believe`
    },
    {
        id: 34,
        question: `When was the FBLA-Middle Level Division established?`,
        options: [`1994`, `1990`, `1997`],
        answer: `1994`
    },
    {
        id: 35,
        question: `How many votes would a chapter of 99 members have at the National Leadership Conference?`,
        options: [`5`, `7`, `3`],
        answer: `3`
    },
    {
        id: 36,
        question: `The fiscal year of FBLA-PBL is July 1- June 30`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 37,
        question: `The last "I believe" paragraph begins with: "I believe I have the _________."`,
        options: [`Courage`, `Duty`, `Responsibility`],
        answer: `Responsibility`
    },
    {
        id: 38,
        question: `According to the FBLA goals, students will "Strengthen the confidence of students in themselves and their`,
        options: [`Work`, `Peers`, `Community`],
        answer: `Work`
    },
    {
        id: 39,
        question: `What is the flagship publication for FBLA and the FBLA- Middle Level students and advisers?`,
        options: [`Tomorrow's Business Leader`, `Tomorrow's Leaders`],
        answer: `Tomorrow's Business Leader`
    },
    {
        id: 40,
        question: `How many times a year is Tomorrow's Business Leader Published?`,
        options: [`4`, `1`, `2`],
        answer: `4`
    },
    {
        id: 41,
        question: `Article 5 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Organization`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 42,
        question: `Article 2 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Membership`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 43,
        question: `Article 2 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Purpose`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 44,
        question: `Article 6 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Dues and Finance`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 45,
        question: `Article 9 of FBLA National Bylaws is about National Executive Council`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 46,
        question: `Article 4 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Emblems and Colors`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `False`
    },
    {
        id: 47,
        question: `Article 11 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Emblems and Colors`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 48,
        question: `Article 7 of FBLA National Bylaws is about Duties of National Officers`,
        options: [`True`, `False`],
        answer: `True`
    },
    {
        id: 49,
        question: `In the absence of the president and vice-president at a regular meeting, who should call
        the meeting to order?`,
        options: [`Secretary`, `Treasurer`, `Comptroller`],
        answer: `Secretary`
    }





    







    

]